https://ntrepidcorp.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
LAST UPDATED: August 6, 2018
Ntrepid Corporation (“Ntrepid” “we,” “our,” or “us”) Privacy Statement —Highlights
Here at Ntrepid we know how much you value privacy, and we realize that you care about what happens to the information you provide to us or that we collect through our website, mobile applications, email, and other sources (our “Systems”) as well as information collected from third parties. We have provided highlights below regarding how we collect, use, and share your information. Click here to see our full Privacy Statement.
Please note that the policies described in the Privacy Statement and this summary do not apply to content that you upload or import to our Systems after purchasing Ntrepid products. That information is governed by the Terms of Service that you receive when making your purchase(s).
What Information Does Ntrepid Collect?
We collect the following types of information:
Information you provide to us when you contact us or in order to use our products and services, such as your contact information, information you provide when signing up for promotions, payment information, and product preferences.
Information that is automatically collected when you use our Systems, such as when you visit our website or cookie information.
Information about you that we receive from affiliates and other third party sources (including other users of our Systems).
Read more about the information we collect.
How does Ntrepid use my information?
We use your information for the following purposes:
Providing products, content, content suggestions, services, and support;
Maintaining the security and integrity of our Systems (including maintaining internal records);
Establishing and verifying the identity and eligibility of users;
Opening, maintaining, administering, managing, and servicing user profiles, accounts or memberships;
Processing, servicing or enforcing transactions (including credit or debit card transactions);
Providing users with product, service, Systems, or company updates;
Responding to your inquiries or comments, or contacting you as necessary;
Analyzing and improving our products, services, or Systems (including developing new products and services; improving safety; managing our communications; analyzing our products; performing market research and tracking our marketing effectiveness; performing data analytics; and performing accounting, auditing and other internal functions);
Conforming to legal requirements or industry standards, complying with legal process, detecting and preventing fraud or misuse, defending our legal rights, or protecting others;
As part of a merger, acquisition, transfer, sale, corporate change, bankruptcy, or any other transaction involving all or a portion of Ntrepid’s assets;
Conducting special events, sweepstakes, surveys, programs, contests, and other offers (and communicating with you about such events); and
Marketing and advertising our products or services as well as products and services of third parties (such as affiliates, subsidiaries, and business partners)
Read more about how we use your information.
How does Ntrepid share my information?
We may share aggregated data about you that does not identify you directly with third parties for any purpose, including marketing.  However, we will only share your personal information that specifically identifies you as follows:
With third party service providers or business partners to help us with our business functions;
If necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of us, our users, or employees, or when required by law;
With your consent;
If the ownership or control of Ntrepid or some or all of its assets changes (including through merger, acquisition, transfer, sale, corporate change, bankruptcy or any other transaction involving all or a portion of Ntrepid’s assets), we may transfer your information to the new owner
Read more about how we share your information.
Ntrepid Privacy Statement—Full Statement
Ntrepid Corporation (“Ntrepid,” “we,” “our,” or “us”) respects your concerns about privacy and values the relationship we have with you.  This Privacy Statement describes the types of information we collect about and from individuals who visit our website or otherwise communicate with us (collectively, “you”). This Privacy Statement also describes how we use the information, with whom we share it, the choices available to you regarding our use of the information, and how you can contact us about our privacy practices.
To What Information Does This Privacy Statement Apply?
This Privacy Statement applies to the collection, use, and disclosure of information from and about you by Ntrepid on Ntrepid’s website (www.ntrepidcorp.com), through our mobile applications, and through telephone, email communications, and other sources (collectively, our “Systems”), as well as information collected by third parties. Ntrepid’s mobile applications will collect the same information identified in this Privacy Statement and that information will be used and shared as stated in this Privacy Statement.
This Privacy Statement does not apply to content that you upload or import to our Systems after purchasing Ntrepid products. That information is governed by the Terms of Service that you receive when making your purchase.
This Privacy Statement also does not apply to third party websites that may be accessible through hyperlinks on our Systems, which have their own privacy statement. Linking to a third party site does not mean that we endorse the site, any products or services described on the site, or any other material contained in a that site. To the extent any linked websites you visit are not owned or controlled by us, we are not responsible for the sites’ content, any use of the sites, or the privacy practices of the sites.  Please review the privacy statement on those other websites to see how they handle your information.
If you choose to use our Systems in any way, such as browsing or interacting, you agree with the terms of our current Privacy Statement as posted here. If you do not agree with this Privacy Statement, you should not use our Systems. We may update or modify this Privacy Statement from time to time at our sole discretion, and will note the date of last update on the top of this page. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed, as your continued use of our Systems following the posting of changes to these terms means that you consent to such changes.
What Information Does Ntrepid Collect?
We may obtain information about you from various sources. We may collect this information when you provide directly through our website, mobile applications, telephone or email communication, or at one of our events. We may also collect information about you from third parties. When you use our Systems, we may also collect certain information about your device or usage by automated means or by using technologies such as cookies, web server logs, and web beacons.
Information that You or Others Provide
You may choose to provide information to us in a number of ways, such as when you participate in an offer or promotion, when you register on our System, when you contact us, or when you otherwise interact on our Systems. The types of information you may provide to us include:
Information required to register your use of our products and services or when you contact us, such as your name, address, city, state, ZIP code, email address telephone number, and other information that you provide;
Information provided voluntarily by you when signing up for promotions (such as birth date, household information, income, marital status, and education);
Financial and payment information if you use our Systems to make or receive payments (such as payment card number, expiration date, account number, and billing address); and
Product preferences, advertisement preferences, and other information about how you use our Systems.
We may also collect your email address through our website for employment-related matters. Additional employment information may be collected by a third party whose data practices Ntrepid does not control.
If you provide us with information regarding another individual, we will assume that you have that person’s consent to give us his or her information. In addition, we may collect information about you that is provided to us by other users of our Systems and other third parties.
Information Collected Automatically
When you visit our Systems or our online advertisements, utilize our services, open an email that we send you, or interact with the communication features on our Systems, we may collect information about your usage or device by automated means or by using technologies such as cookies, web server logs, and web beacons. Some of the technologies we use to collect information automatically collected include:
Cookies: Cookies are small text files that websites send to your computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify your browser or to store information or settings in your browser. We may use cookies that are managed by Ntrepid or by third parties for the purposes provided in this Privacy Statement, including for session management, authentication, user preference storage, Systems performance and personalization, Systems analytics, advertising (including affiliate marketing), content management, eCommerce, search, and social media integration.
Web server logs: In conjunction with obtaining information through cookies, our web servers may log details regarding your device, operating system, or information about your usage of our Systems.
Web beacons and pixels: We may place tags on our Systems or in emails called “web beacons” or “pixels.” These are computer instructions that link web pages to particular web servers and their cookies. Web beacons and pixels can be used to track the pages you view, links that you click, or other online behavior. These tools have a number of uses, such as measuring the effectiveness of our email campaigns and online advertisements (both on our Systems and on third party websites).
Other: In addition to cookies, web server logs, and web beacons, we may use other technologies to collect information for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement.
These technologies may permit collection of information such as demographic data, browser type, MAC address and other device information, operating system type and settings, domain, the address of the web page that linked you to our website, IP address, pages visited, whether you have visited us before or are new to the website, activities conducted on the page (such as search queries), and the day and time of your visit.
We also collect information about you and your interactions with social media and other third party websites, which we may merge or enhance with other information we collect about you for the purposes described below in this Privacy Statement.
At this time, we do not honor “do not track” signals from website browsers. However, you may refuse or delete cookies.  If you do so, some of the functionality of our website may be impaired. Additionally, you may still be identifiable and your usage may still be trackable by other means. Please refer to your browser “Help” instructions to learn more about how to manage cookies and the use of similar technologies.
How Does Ntrepid Use My Information?
We use your information for the following purposes:
Providing products, content, content suggestions, services, and support;
Maintaining the security and integrity of our Systems, including maintaining internal records;
Establishing and verifying the identity and eligibility of users;
Opening, maintaining, administering, managing, and servicing user profiles, accounts or memberships;
Processing, servicing or enforcing transactions (including credit or debit card transactions);
Providing users with product, service, Systems, or company updates;
Responding to your inquiries or comments, or contacting you as necessary;
Analyzing and improving our products, services, or Systems (including developing new products and services; improving safety; managing our communications; analyzing our products; performing market research and tracking our marketing effectiveness; performing data analytics; and performing accounting, auditing and other internal functions);
Conforming to legal requirements or industry standards, complying with legal process, detecting and preventing fraud or misuse, defending our legal rights, or protecting others;
As part of a merger, acquisition, transfer, sale, corporate change, bankruptcy, or any other transaction involving all or a portion of Ntrepid’s assets;
Conducting special events, sweepstakes, surveys, programs, contests, and other offers (and communicating with you about such events); and
Marketing and advertising our products or services as well as products and services of third parties (such as affiliates, subsidiaries, and business partners).
How Does Ntrepid Share My Information?
We may share aggregated data about you that does not identify you directly with third parties for any purpose, including marketing.  However, we will only share your personal information that specifically identifies you as follows:
We may disclose your information to third parties who help us with our business functions, such as service providers or suppliers, and with business partners. Such third parties are not authorized to use or disclose your information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. Examples of service providers include entities that process credit card and other types of payments, or entities that provide web hosting or analytics services.
We may contract with third-party advertising networks that collect information about you through the use of cookies, web server logs, and web beacons on our Systems and emails; on third-party websites and emails; and on our advertising placed on third-party websites. We and these third parties use this information to provide advertisements about products and services tailored to your interests (including for companies not affiliated with us). You may see these advertisements on other websites.
We may share your information if necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of us, our customers, or employees, or when otherwise required by law. We may also share your information with your consent in certain circumstances.
We reserve the right to transfer your information in the event we sell, transfer, or engage in another transaction involving all or a portion of our business or assets, or undertake another form of corporate change, including bankruptcy. Following such a sale, transfer, transaction, or corporate change, you may contact the entity to which we transferred your information with any inquiries concerning the processing of that information.
Your information may be stored in databases maintained by Ntrepid (including local storage) or third parties, and may be disclosed to third parties for the purposes stated in this Privacy Statement, that are located within and outside the United States, including countries where privacy rules differ and may be less stringent than those of the country in which you reside.
Is My Information Secure?
Ntrepid will take reasonable precautions to protect your information from loss, misuse, or alteration. Please be aware, however, that any email or other transmission you send through the Internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception.
Does Ntrepid Collect Information From Children?
Ntrepid does not intentionally collect information from children under 13 years of age, and children under age 13 should not submit any information to us. If we become aware that a child has provided us with information without parental consent, or a parent or guardian of a child contacts us through the contact information provided below, we will use reasonable efforts to delete the child’s information from our databases.
What Choices Do I Have?
We want to communicate with you about our products and services and make content available to you, but only in the ways that you agree to hear from us. You may “opt-out,” or unsubscribe from our newsletters, special offers or discounts, or other marketing communications by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email or other communication you receive from us.  After doing so, you will not receive future promotional emails unless you open a new account, enter a contest, or sign up to receive newsletters or emails. You may also continue to receive non-marketing communications about your account or purchases that you have made. Please allow up to 2 weeks to process your request.
We store data for as long as it is necessary to provide the products and services described in this Privacy Statement, as required by law, and for our internal business purposes. If you would like us to delete your data, you may contact us using the information below, and we will make reasonable efforts to accommodate your request.
How Can I Contact Ntrepid?
Ntrepid is committed to working with you to obtain a fair and rapid resolution of any queries, complaints, or disputes about privacy. If you have submitted information to Ntrepid and you would like to have it deleted from our databases or corrected, or if you have any other questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, please email us at legal@ntrepidcorp.com for more information.
Effective Date:  August 6, 2018
COVID-19 Measures
Mission
Leadership
Careers
Blog
Events
Contact Us
Semimonthly Virtual Training & Expert Lectures for OSINT Operators—Supporting Critical Missions Remotely
Learn More
